泰皮来劲! 泰皮来劲! 泰皮真来劲!
Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy!
噢!泰皮真热情有劲啦!
ohhh, Tappy's got juice! Tappy's got juice!
噢!泰皮!
Whoa, Tappy!
来劲! 来劲! 来劲!
Juice! Juice! Juice!
你真来劲! 你真来劲!
Juice by you! Juice by you!
热情有劲! 谢谢!
Juice! Juice by you! Thank you, thank you..
- 赢家出来了. - 我们有了个赢家
- We got a winner. - We got a winner.
- 我说 我们有了个赢家. - 我们有了个赢家!
- I said, we got a winner. - We got a winner!
我们有了个赢家!
We got a winner!
第一名她是来自华盛顿的飞行员
She's a flight attendant from Washington, DC.
欢迎玛丽 肯林顿
Please welcome Mary Kellington.
玛丽热情有劲! 玛丽热情有劲! 哦…
Juice by Mary! Juice by Mary! Whoa...
不要动电视的脑筋
Harold, please, not again the TV.
妈! 别这样 妈!
Ma! Come on, Ma!
你为什么要这样小题大作呢?
Why do you have to make a big deal outta this?
你知道我们几个小时内
You know you'll get the set back
就可以把它要回来
in a couple of hours.
为什么要让我觉得如此愧疚呢 妈?!
Why you gotta make me feel so guilty, Ma?!
天呀! 你在做什么?
Jesus! What are you doing?
你想让我弄坏电视
Trying to get me to break my own mother's set?
或天线吗?
Or radiator?
还是炸掉整个屋子?
And maybe blow up the house?
我是你的儿子,你的血肉耶,妈!
Im your own son!Your own flesh and blood!
你要这样对待你的儿子吗?
Is that what you're trying to do? Your son?
为什么老是跟我玩游戏呢?
Why you play games with my head,
莫名其妙!
for Christ's sake?
哈瑞 我不会这样做的
Harold, I wouldn't do that.
那链子不是针对你的. 是防小偷用的
The chain isn't for you. It's for the robbers.
那你怎么不出来?
Then why won't you come out?
知道我的意思吗? 知道你让我有多不开心吗 妈?
See what I mean? See how you always upset me, Ma?
真是的
Christ's sake.
妈?
Ma?
妈!
Ma!
出来嘛. 好不好 妈?
Come on out. Please, Ma?
随你去吧!
Ah, screw it!
这不会再发生了
This isn't happening.
如果还是会发生的话,
And if it should be happening,
那也好
it would be all right.
所以别担心 西蒙. 一切都会没事的
So don't worry, Seymour. It'll all work out.
你已经看过了. 最后还是会没事的
You'll see already. In the end, it's all nice.
妈的! 老兄.
Shit, man.
这玩意开始
That motherfucker's starting
有点零散了
to look a little seedy.
你怎么突然挑惕起来了?
You particular all of a sudden?
我对女朋友无所谓,
I don't care my girlfriend go hell,
只要能得到我们的面包
just as long as we get our bread.
来帮我吧 泰隆
Just give me a hand, Tyrone.
你看
Look at that.
- 哈罗. - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
连桌子也干来啦!
Fuck, the table too!
你要我怎么样呢?
What do you want for me?
背着过来吗?
You want me to schlep it on my back?
- 你有朋友呀.
- You got a friend.
- 我可不是搬运工
- I ain't my leper's schlepper shit.
这款儿子.
Such a son.
你妈生个蛋
Your mother needs you
还比较划算
like a moose needs a hat rack.
靠! 老兄
Shit, man.
真是高档货呀,宝贝
This is some boss scag, baby.
- 我觉得 超赞的.
- I mean, dynamite.
- 噢 老兄 真的很特别
- Oh, man, it's something else.
你知道我门该怎么做吗?
You know what we need to do?
我们要弄整块的
We need to get us a piece of this Brody shit,
分散之后再卖出去!
cut it up and off it!
我们很容易就赚双倍
We could double our money... easy.
一些卖给别人
They maybe buy some pieces
一些自己用
and we got some whole other never shit coming off
这样做才对
That'd be righteous.
我打赌很快
I'll bet in no time off
我们会拿整磅纯货
we'd get a pound of pure
直接通过药头
straight from Sal the Geep.
噢!
Oooh!
我就是这个意思, 豪无疑问
That's what I'm talking about, baby - no hassles.
- 还好吧? - 有事吗 老哥?
- How's it goin'? - What's up, buddy?
- 一如往常. - 嗯 那还不错
- The usual? - Yeah, sounds good.
要点别的吗? 喂?
Anything else? Huh?
- 还要什么吗? - 喔 不了
- Anything else? - Ah, no.
没事.我很好
Nothing. I'm all right.
- 午安 哥德太太.
- Good afternoon, Mrs Goldfarb.
- 午安 拉宾先生
- Good afternoon, Mr Rabinowitz.
不过我不确定有多好 你呢?
Although I'm not so sure how good it is. And you?
- 我能说什么呢? 你想要回电视?
- What can I say? You want your TV?
- 是的 如果你不介意的话
- Yes, if you don't mind.
哥德太太 我能请教你一件事吗?
Mrs Goldfarb, can I ask you a question?
希望你别太在意
You won't take it personal?
我们认识几年了?
How many years we know each other?
谁在乎呢?
Who's to count?
你为何不报警处理呢?
Why not tell ready the police?
也许他们会跟哈瑞谈谈
Maybe they could talk to Harry.
- 你就再也不会有电视被偷了.
- He wouldn't be stealing no more the TV.
- 我不能这样做
- I couldn't do that.
哈瑞是我唯一的孩子. 他是我的一切
Harry's my only child. He's all I have.
谢谢你,拉宾先生
Thank you, Mr Rabinowitz.
'加入我们并创造惊奇. JUICE!'
'Join us in creating excellence. JUICE!'
'你会有更多难以想象 生命的热情'
'You have more passion for living.'
'兴奋! 兴奋吧!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!
'兴奋! 兴奋起来吧!
'兴奋!兴奋吧!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!
'兴奋! 兴奋起来吧!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!'
'他们来劲吗?'
'They got the juice?'
- '是的 他们真来劲!' - '振奋吧.'
- 'Yeah, they got the juice!' - 'Juice it up.'
'哈罗? 是谁呀?'
'Hello? Who is it?'
呃 妈的. 现在呢?
Aw, shit. Now what?
哈罗?
Hello?
- '莎拉哥德太太吗?' - 是我,请说
- 'Mrs Sara Goldfarb?' - Me. Speaking.
我是马林集团的罗素赖尔
This is lyle Russell from Maylin and Block.
- 我没有兴趣.
- I'm not interested.
- '等一下. 我不是要推销东西
- 'Wait. I'm not selling anything.
'我只是要给你一个机会
'I just want to offer you a chance
上电视'
to be on television.'
上电视?
Television?
'是的,哥德太太. 恭喜你!'
'That's right, Mrs Goldfarb. Congratulations!'
- 不过我没有任何…
- look, I don't have any...
- '我不是为钱,哥德太太
- 'I don't want money Mrs Goldfarb.
'我打电话来告诉你,你赢了
'I'm calling to tell you you've already won.
'马林集团为大部份电视节目
'Maylin and Block discovers contestants
寻找参赛者
for TV shows.
'你从一长串名单中被选中了-
'You've been chosen from a long list -
'也就是说 你赢了!'
'meaning, you've already won.'
- 噢… - '是的,哥德太太'
- Ohh... - 'Yes, Mrs Goldfarb.'
我从没想过会上电视 我只是…
I never thought I'd be on television. I'm just...
'没错. 你会上电视
'That's right. You, on television.
'我们会把所有的资料寄给你
'We'll send you the necessary information.
'再见 恭喜 请保重'
'Goodbye, congratulations and take care.'
可是我不懂
But I don't get it.
你为什么对你父母苛求?
Why are you so hard on your folks?
我是说 他门给你每样东西
I mean, they give you everything.
供你吃
They hook you up with an apartment,
,供你住
a croaker shrink.
那很好 你知道的. 很棒. 只是…
Which is fine, you know. It's great. It's just...
钱从不是我真正想向他们要的东西
money is never what I really wanted from them,
你懂吗?
you know?
钱对他们来说太多了
That's pretty much all they have to give.
为什么不离开他们?
Why don't you get away from 'em?
- 我要怎么做呢? - 我不知道
- How am I gonna do that? - I don't know.
何不利用你的衣服?
What about your clothes?
你图画得不错. 可以开个店
Your sketches are great. Open up a store.
- 我不行. - 为什么?
- I can't. - Why not?
这样我怎么有时间跟你在一起?
When will I have time to hang with you?
- 哇! 要在哪开派对?
- Well! So where's the party?
- 我一告诉你 你会吓得跳出窗外
- When I tell you, you're gonna die.
这里紧了点
This is a tough one.
我有本不错的减重书
I got a great diet book.
嘿
Hey.
他们来了
They're coming.
'振奋! 振奋吧!'
'Be excited! Be, be excited!'
我想我应该晒点太阳
I thought I'd catch a little sun today.
是吗? 我想上电视时会有打光
Really? Well, in a box you'll catch it.
只管放松自己 想
Just relax and think how gorgeous
想你新染的红发有多亮丽
you'll look with your new red hair.
今天先照顾头发,明天再管阳光
Today the hair, tomorrow the sun.
有谁想浪费时间吗?
Anybody wanna waste some time?
'天使说现在就是最佳时机'
'Angel says this is time wish do it now.'
'我明天会打给布迪' '布敌是谁?'
- 'she'll call Brody tomorrow.' - 'whos Brody?'
'他是我可爱的药头,
-that's my sweet connects
有超赞的玩意'
-'He gets unbelievable shit.'
'正点'
- 'Righteous.'
'玛丽,我们有个想法' '什么?'
- 'look, we got this idea.' - 'What is it?'
'弄整块的毒品,
'Get a piece of stuff,
分割开来倍增我们的钱'
cut it up and double our money.no problem'
'然后搞个整磅的纯货后退休
'Then get a pound of pure and retire.
'你知道这个意思'
'You know what that means.'
'我们不用再辛苦了 日子就好过了'
'We get off hard knocks and on easy street.'
到底要做什么?
What's the catch?
那是红的. 我是说 是红的
That's a red. I mean, that's a red.
不是纯红, 但那是红的
It's not a red red, but that's a red. It's a red.
- 红的? - 是呀,是红的
- Red? - Yeah. It's a red.
- 你是说这是红的? - 是的
- You're telling me that's red? - Yeah.
那橘色是什么?
Then what's orange?
如果这是红的, 我想知道 - 橘色是什么?
If this is a red, I want to know - what's orange?
嗯 它也可以…
Well, it could be...
算是有点偏橘
that it's a little orange too.
你知道吗?
You know something?
我总是在想
I always thought
你是我见过最美的女孩
you were the most beautiful girl I ever seen.
是吗?
Really?
从我第一眼见到你
Ever since I first saw you.
那很好呀 哈瑞
That's nice, Harry.
我觉得很开心
That makes me feel really good.
从前也有人对我这样说过
Other people have told me that before,
不过都没啥意义
and it was meaningless.
为什么?
Why?
因为你觉得 他们在逗你开心?
Because you thought they were pulling your leg?
不 不是这样. 我的意思是…
No, no, not like that. I mean...
不知道.
I don't know.
我不知道 或说我跟本不在乎是如何
I don't know or even care if they were.
只是从他们口中说出来…
Just from them it was...
就是毫无意义 懂吗?
just meaningless, you know?
当你说时 我听到了
When you say it, I hear it.
真的听到了
I really hear it.
像你这样的女孩
Somebody like you
能够真的带给我好运
could really make things all right for me.
你这样想?
You think?
这是什么?
What is it?
记得我告诉过你开店的事吗?
Remember when I told you about the store?
嗯
Yeah.
我一直思考了好久…
I've been thinking about it and...
我找了一些资料 而且…
I put together some numbers and...
这不是不可能的事!
and it's not impossible!
我是说 你知道吗 你可以做的
I mean, you know, you could do it.
你应该做的!
You should do it!
我的意思是 我们可以一起来做
I mean, we could do it together.
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
够了
Stop already.
你穿红礼服会比
You'll feel better in the red dress than
吃起司面包快乐
in the cheese Danish.
'我做了叁件事改变了我的生活. 叁件事.'
'Three things changed my life. Three.'
'第一! 不吃红肉!'
'Number one! No red meat!'
'想想看. 为何有人锺情红肉?
'Think about it. What do they stick in red meat?
'我吃红肉
'I ate red meat to the point
到了整块生吃的地步
where I would eat it... right off, raw.
'我喜欢肉! 但我彻底改变
'I loved my meat! I turned it around.
'你要坚定.
'You need to be committed.
你要有热忱
You need to be passionate.
'叁十天不吃红肉. 不吃红肉!
'No red meat for 30 days. No red meat!
'做了叁件事改变了我的生活
'Three things is all I did to change my life.
叁件事'
Three things.'
艾达告诉我们了. 真是太好了
Ada told us. It's gorgeous.
我们明天要把颜色弄深一点
We're gonna make it darker tomorrow.
- 为什么? - 好搭配我的红礼服
- Why? - To go with my red dress.
- 可是现在看起来像玛丹娜.
- But it's looking like Madonna.
- 我不是玛丹娜
- It's not Madonna.
我也不是
And neither is this.
不过我很快会进行节食
But soon - I'm going on a diet.
- 怎样的节食? - 蛋跟葡萄柚
- What diet? - Eggs and grapefruit.
- 我试过这套. 真是万幸 - 没有那么遭
- I was on that. Lots of luck. - It's not so bad.
- 你进行节食多久了? - 整天
- How long you been on it? - All day.
整天! 现在是下午一点!
All day! It's one o'clock!
- 我想要瘦. - 她想要瘦
- Thinking thin. - She's thinking thin.
我们家路易丝 就像那样甩了50磅
My louise, she lost 50lbs just like that.
像怎样? 娘娘腔
- like what? - Poof!
你把她放干燥箱吗?
Did you put her in a sweatbox?
他去看医生 医生给他药
She went to a doctor. He gave her pills.
你不会想吃的
You don't want to eat.
所以呢? 你的意思是可以坐在这
So? You mean, I'm sitting here
不去想面包上的熏肉吗?
not thinking about pastrami on rye?
你不该在有人节食的时后这样说的
Don't talk like that when someone's on a diet.
没什么啦. 我会再偷吃片葡萄柚吧
Big deal. I'll sneak another wedge of grapefruit.
- 我是想瘦! - 噢 莎拉 邮差来了
- I'm thinking thin! - Ooh, Sara, the mailman.
哥德莎拉? 你有哥德莎拉的信件吗?
Sara Goldfarb? You have something for me?
我在等我的信
I'm expecting something.
哥德 哥德. 哥德莎拉
Goldfarb, Goldfarb. Sara Goldfarb.
- 是这封吗? - 就是这封!
- Is that it? - That's it!
- 快点. - 等一下,我拿东西
- Come on. - I gotta get my stuff.
- 好的. - 我可以教你
- All right. - I can tell you.
名字. 填上你的名字
Your name. Put your name.
S-A-R-A G-O-l-D…
S-A-R-A G-O-L-D...
F-A-R-B!
吓吓叫?
Dynamite?
吓吓叫的
It's dynamite.
阿哈! 吓吓叫!
A-ha! Dynamite!
没问题 我们马上过去
All right, we on our way.
- 布迪的人说有高档货了
- Brody's man says it's fine shit.
- 好吧 老兄
- All right, man.
- 就是这样. - 嘿 泰?
- Here we go. - Hey, Ty?
- 我们不能出差错 老兄
- let's do this right, man.
- 哎呦 宝贝. 当然的
- Come on, baby. Naturally.
- 快点 我们快点
- Hurry, hurry. Let's hurry.
- 不知道你们有没有听到
- I wonder when you'll hear.
- 嗨! - 我想跟你去!
- Hi! - I wanna come with you!
也许她们会送你
Maybe they'll send you to
到绿茵小舍 明星都会到那里去
the Tavern On The Green with the stars.
嗯 我要在那里吃蛋跟葡萄柚
Yeah, eggs and grapefruit at Tavern On The Green.
- 我希望他们有提供
- I hope they have that.
- 趁邮差还没来快点
- Hurry before the mailman comes.
- 好了 - 寄出去吧!
- Here we are. - Mail it!
噢 莎拉!
Oh, Sara!
- 在这里 老兄 - 阿?
- There it is, Jim. - Huh?
- 在这里 宝贝 - 噢 靠!
- There it is, baby. - Oh, shit!
- 要试试吗? - 等等 泰
- Shall we try it? - Wait, Ty.
听着 这是我们发财的机会
Look, this is our chance to make it big.
我们好好做, 可以弄到整磅的纯货
We play it right, we can get a pound of pure.
可是如果我们浪费了…
But if we get wasted...
- 一切就搞砸了 - 我知道
- we'll fuck it up. - Right on.
嘿 听我说 我不是想愚弄你 老兄
Hey, look, I ain't trying to jive you, Jim.
我不希望一辈子在接上打混
I dont wanna be running the streets my whole life
挨冻受饿
my nose runnin' down to my chin.
我的意思是我们先尝一下
All I'm sayin' is take a little taste
才知道该怎么分装
so we know how much to cut.
纯为生意
It's business.
嗯 有道理
Yeah, fair enough.
靠…
Shit...
'谢谢大家! 我只做了叁件事
'Thank you! Three things is all I did.
'只需花叁十天
'30 days is all it takes.
'第二! 不吃精制糖!
'Number two! No refined sugar!
'现在 糖无所不在
'Now, sugar's everywhere.
'你知道吗? 商家在瓶装水里也放了糖
'You know they even put sugar in bottled water?
'我曾得了嗜糖症! 那曾是我的药
'I was sick with sugar! That was my medicine.
'它浸蚀着我的大脑
'It nurtured my spiralling brain
让我觉得是个输家'
that felt I was a loser.'
'振作起来!'
'Juice by you!'
'第二条守则就是不吃精糖
'Rule two is no refined sugar.
'汽水? 汽水连想都不要想
'Sodas? Don't even think about sodas any more.
'不要再舔任何糖果了
'No sucking candies. None of that.
只管远离它
Just stay away from it.
'30天没有糖的生活'
'No refined sugar. For 30 days.'
'我要吃得正确
'I'm gonna eat right.
'我要提起我的精神
'I am gonna pick up my spirits
我将放手一搏
and I am gonna try!
'我找到了希望.
'I found hope.
在希望中找到了方法…'
And in that hope, I found a way...'
别再说了!
Shut up!
'哈罗?'
'Hello?'
- 露西? - '是'
- Rosie? - 'Yeah.'
- 我是莎拉. - '嗯?'
- Sara. - 'Yeah?'
我想跟你要那位医生的电话
I need the number of that doctor.
我不了解为何你要去见他
I don't understand why you gotta see him.
真他妈的
Cut the son of a bitch loose, for Christ's sake.
因为我不想他跟我爸妈
Because he'll tell my parents
提到我停止治疗的事
that I've stopped therapy.
它们已经对我很不爽 打算跟我断绝,你知道吗?
They're already thinking of cutting me off.
哈瑞 我不会跟他上床什么的
Harry, I'm not gonna sleep with him.
演唱会节束我就会回来了
I'm gonna come home after the concert.
你在吃醋!
You're jealous!
哈瑞吃醋?
Harry - jealous?
- 抱住我 - 不要
- Put your arms around me. - No.
你真不听话! 抱住我
You are so stubborn! Put your arms around me.
别玩了!
Stop that!
- 我要把你眼球吸出来 - 嗯
- I'll suck your eyeballs out. - Mm-hm.
唔…
Well...
我很失望你不怎么自在
I'm disappointed that you're indisposed.
安妮塔有出外什么的吗?
Is Anita out of town or something?
为什么问呢?
Why do you ask?
我只是想知道她是不是不自“在”
I was just wondering if she was "indisposed".
没有
No.
她很好 谢谢你
She's fine, thank you.
事实上 她在佛罗里达
Actually, she's in Florida.
- 我可以问一个私人问题吗,亚诺? - 当然
- Can I ask you something, Arnold? - Of course.
任何东西. 什么?
Anything. What?
- 你这里沾了东西 - 没有了吗?
- You just have something here. - Gone?
下面一点 再下来一点
A little bit, a little bit lower.
没事了. 别担心 好多了
It's OK. Don't worry. It's much better.
亚诺!
Arnold!
你觉得如何 哥德太太?
How are you, Mrs Goldfarb?
我如何? 身躯庞大 所以我才会来这
How am I? Enormous. That's why I'm here.
- 我看过情况更遭的 - 噢…谢谢
- I've seen much worse. - Oh... thank you.
- 你的听力跟视力如何? - 我两个都有
- How's your hearing and vision? - I have both.
医师等一下就来
The doctor will be with you shortly.
- 你有点过重 - 有点?
- You're a little overweight. - A little?
我想捐50磅出来
I have 50lbs I'm willing to donate.
我们会处理的 没问题
We can take care of that. No problem.
我们要发了 宝贝
We're on our way, baby.
我们要发了!
We are on our way!
天呀 在那里真棒
God, It was great out there.
我的意思是每个人都很  渴
I mean, everybody is thirsty.
过来
Come to me.
哈瑞! 我好高兴
Harry! I am so glad.
自然地
Naturally.
紫色早上吃
Purple in the morning.
蓝色是下午
Blue in the afternoon.
晚上吃橘色的
orange in the evening.
这是我的叁餐 神气的家伙
There's my three meals, Mr Smarty-pants.
绿色夜里吃 就像那样
And green at night. Just like that.
一 二  叁 四
one, two, three, four.
怎么不回床上来? 亲爱的
Come back to bed, baby.
等一下 艾利丝 有的是时间
Come on now, Alice. Got plenty of time for that.
现在
Right now
我正在装配新的活门镜子
I'm grooving with these new mirrors I got.
呼!
Oooh!
妈 我跟你说 我以后一定要成大事
I told ya, Mom, one day I'd make it.
你什么都不用做 我的宝贝
You don't have to make anything, my sweet.
你只要爱你妈妈就好,嗯
You just have to love your mama, huh?
你在做什么 亲爱的?
What ya doin', baby?
喔?
Huh?
- 你在做什么 亲爱的? - 没什么
- What ya doin', baby? - Nothin'.
只是在想你
Just thinkin' about you.
在想我要跟你做的下流事
About the nasty things I'm about to do to ya.
我要上你了
Bitch, get over here!
泰 你吓到我了
Ty, you scare me to death.
没有,我没有吓你
No, I wouldn't scare you.
我不想吓任何人
I don't wanna scare nobody.
我只想生命中
All I want out of life
有点平静与快乐 ,仅此而已
is a bit of peace and happiness. That's all.
就是现在…
Right now...
你是我见过最漂亮的美人
you're the finest fox I ever laid my eyes on.
- 那是我要做的事 - 咦?
- That's what I'll do. - Hmm?
为了我妈
For my mother.
我一直在想
I've been thinking about
买个东西给她
getting something for her.
像是一件礼物什么的
Like... a present or something.
但我不知道要给她什么
But I didn't know what I was gonna get,
直到现在
until now.
- 所以? - 后来我问我自己
- And? - I finally asked myself, right,
她着迷什么?
what's her fix?
电视机 对吧?
Television, right?
如果有谁是电视迷 那她一定是个老太太
If ever there's a TV junkie, it's the old lady.
我想我欠她一台新电视机
I owe her a new set,
之前老是搬来搬去
with all the wear and tear it got
全是磨损和伤痕
being schlepped back and forth to old Abe's.
你真的很爱她 是吧?
You really love her, don't you?
我想是吧. 你知道吗?
I-I guess so. You know?
我一直希望她快乐
Most of the time I just want her to be happy.
我们现在去买一台
Let's go get it now.
先离开吧
Let's push off first.
现在还早 哈瑞.
It's early, Harry.
我们晚上再出发
We shouldn't get going till tonight.
'兴奋吧. 兴奋吧
'Be excited. Be, be excited.
兴奋 兴奋吧!
'兴奋吧
'Be excited.
'要坚决而热忱'
'Be committed and be passionate.'
'我是活生生的例子 瘦了65磅
'I am a living testament. 65 lbs thinner.
感觉太好了!
I feel great!
'第叁. 噢 第叁项!
'Number three. Ohhh, number three!
'这个让很多发疯
'This drives most people crazy.
'目前为止都很容易
'This is easy so far.'
- 瘦了 - 她跟以前不一样了
- That is thin! - She's not the same person.
我快要可以穿那件红礼服了
I can almost zip the red dress.
差不多可以把拉  拉上了
I've almost got the zipper up.
- 邮差来了! - 喂!
- The mailman! - Oh!
我看到你的信的话 我会拿着到处示众
When I see it I'll wave it all over the place.
- 你确定吗? - 是的 我确定
- Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm sure.
- 他说什么呀?
- What did he say?
- 别担心 莎拉 一定会来的
- Don't worry, Sara, it'll come.
是呀 别担心 会来的
Yeah, don't worry. It'll come.
是哈瑞!
It's Harry!
哈瑞 噢!
Harry, oh!
嘿 妈 轻一点 你会把我压碎的
Hey, Ma, easy. You'll crush me, for Christ sakes.
- 进屋吧 - 哈罗
- Come inside. - Hello.
嗨 哈瑞! 哈罗! 有客人来罗!
- Hi, Harry! Hello! - We'll have a little visit.
过得如何呀 哈瑞? 你看起来不错
So, how are you, Harry? You look so good.
- 想吃点什么吗? - 不了 妈
- You want something to eat? - No, Ma.
小点心 还是蛋糕?
A little nosh, a piece of cake?
我可以去弄点来
I could go and get something if you want.
家里没什么东西了
I don't have anything in the house,
不过艾达阿姨那有
but Ada would have.
来个小蛋糕好吗? 要吃点什么吗?
A cupcake? You want something to eat?
不 不用 妈 什么都不用 请坐下吧
No, no, Ma, nothing. Please, sit.
你让我头昏眼花的
You're making me dizzy, for Christ's sake.
你有发现我有啥不同吗? 注意到我变瘦了吗?
You notice anything, huh? You notice I'm slimmer?
嗯 我想是的
Yeah, I guess you are.
25磅 我瘦了25磅耶! 你相信吗?
25lbs, I lost. 25lbs! Can you believe it?
- 而且这才刚开始而已
- And that's only the beginning.
- 那很好 妈 真的很好
- That's great, Ma That's readly great.
我真的很为你高兴
I'm really happy for you.
但是你要不要坐下来? 拜托
But will you sit? Please.
很抱歉我没回家好一阵子了
I'm sorry I haven't been around in a while,
妈 但我一直很忙
Ma, but I've been busy.
是吗? 你有好工作了? 做得好吗?
Yeah? You got a good job? You're doing well?
- 嗯 很好 真的很好 - 什么工作呢?
- Yeah, good, real good. - What kind of business?
嗯 我有点像批发商
Well, I'm sort of a distributor like,
为大进口商做销售
for a big importer.
- 哇! 我真为你高兴!
- Ohh! I'm so happy for you!
- 妈… 轻点. 这样我会死的
- Ma... Easy. You're killin' me.
天呀 你一直在练举重吗?
Jesus, what, you been lifting weights?
- 我知道你办得到的 - 你是对的 妈
- I knew you could do that. - You were right.
现在你可能跟个好女孩恋爱
Now maybe you'll meet a nice girl
顺便生个小孩?
and have a baby?
嗯 我已经认识一个了
Well, I already met one.
妈 别太夸张了
Ma, don't go ape shit.
- 她是谁? 谁家的女孩呢? - 你认识的
- Who is she? Who's her parents? - You know her.
- 玛丽? 玛丽西尔法. 记得吗? - 噢 西尔法!
- Marion? Marion Silver. Remember? - Oh, Silver!
当然. 曼哈顿海滩
of course. Manhattan Beach.
他在布拉格有间房子 做服装生意的
House on the esplanade. Garment business.
嗯. 他是女性内衣的大亨
He's big in women's undies.
妈 被你这么一闹
Before you go bouncing all over again
我都忘记了…
and make me forget, just...
我想告诉你
What I wanna tell you is that
我有件礼物要给你
I got you a present.
我不需要礼物 只要有个小孙子
I don't need a present. Just have a baby.
让我来告诉你好吗?
Will you let me tell you what I got ya?
可以吗 妈?
Will ya, Ma?
天呀 你今天真的有点反常
Christ, you are really something else today,
你知道吗?
you know that?
听我说 我知道…
Look, I know...
嗯…
Well...
很抱歉我一直不学好
I'm sorry for being such a bastard.
我很想补偿你
I wanna make it up.
我是说
I mean,
我知道我不能改变发生过的事
I know I can't change anything that's happened,
但是我希望你知道…
but I want you to know that...
我很爱你 而且我对你很抱歉
That I love ya, and that I'm sorry.
我希望你快乐.
And I want you to be happy.
所以我买了台新电视机给你
So I got you a brand-new TV set.
过几天就会送来了
It's gonna be delivered in a couple of days.
梅西来的喔!
It's from Macy's!
噢 哈瑞!
oh, Harry!
你父亲会很开心的
Your father'd be so happy
如果他看到你
if he could see what you're doing
为妈妈所做的事
for your mother.
看到了吗 西蒙?
See that, Seymour?
你看到你的儿子有多棒了吧?
You see how good your son is?
他知道
He knows
妈妈一个人独居 是什么感觉
what it's like for his mother living all alone.
都没人来看她
No one to visit her.
嘿 妈
Hey, Ma.
- 你在磨牙吗? - 什么?
- You on uppers? - What?
你在磨牙
You're on uppers.
你在吃减肥药 是吗?
You're on diet pills, ain't you?
我跟你说了 我去看专科医生
I told you. I'm going to a specialist.
我想也是! 你让体重急速下降 不是吗?
That's what I thought! You're on speed, ain't ya?
哈瑞 你还好吧 我是去看医生耶
Harry, I'm goin' to a doctor.
- 他给你什么 有给你药片吗?
- Does he give you pills?
- 当然 他是医生呀
- Of course. He's a doctor.
- 什么样的药片?
- What kind of pills?
- 有紫的 有蓝的 还有橘色的…
- A purple, a blue, an orange...
我的意思是 里面含有什么?
I mean, like what's in 'em?
哈瑞 我是莎拉哥德
Oh, Harry, I'm Sara Goldfarb,
又不是爱因斯坦
not Albert Einstein.
怎么知道里面有什么?
How should I know?
那些玩意是不是让你感觉很好 而且充满活力?
Does it make you feel good and give you pep?
嗯… 是吧 有一点
Well... yeah, a little.
妈 我从这里就可以听到你在磨牙的声音
Ma, I can hear ya grinding your teeth.
- 晚上就不会了呀 - 晚上?
- That goes away at night. - At night?
对呀 我吃了绿色药片
Yeah, when I take the green one.
30分钟后就睡着了 真好用
30 minutes I'm asleep. Poof.
妈 妈 你要甩掉这些玩意
Ma, Ma, ya gotta cut that stuff loose.
我可以告诉你 这不是好东西
I'm tellin' ya, it's no good.
怎么会不好呢? 我瘦了25磅耶
What do you mean it's no good? 25lbs I've lost.
那又怎么样? 你想变成毒瘾虫吗?
So what? You wanna be a dope fiend?
毒虫? 我有口吐白沫吗?
Dope fiend? Am I foaming at the mouth?
人家是个好医生
He's a nice doctor.
我告诉你 那家伙一点都不好
I am telling you, he's no good.
你怎么会知道那么多?
How come you know so much?
你怎么会比医生更了解药呢?
How come you know more than a doctor?
相信我 妈 我知道的. 好吗?
Believe me, Ma, I know. All right?
你会慢慢上瘾的
You'll get strung out for creat sick.
噢 别这样嘛! 我快要可以穿那件红礼服了
Ah, come on! I almost fit in my red dress.
就是去参加你高中毕业典礼那件
The one I wore to your high school graduation.
你爸爸好喜欢那件
The one your father liked so much.
噢,
oh,
我记得他看我穿那件时的眼神
I remember how he looked at me in that red dress.
妈 那件红礼服有什么大不了的吗?
Ma, what's the big deal about the red dress?
我要穿它上…
I'm going to wear it at...
你还不知道!
You don't know!
我要上电视了
I'm gonna be on television.
我接到了电话和申请书
I got a call and an application...
噢 妈 谁在跟你开玩笑?
Come on, Ma, who's pulling your leg?
不 不 不. 我跟你说
No, no, no. I'm tellin' ya.
我要上电视当个参赛者
I'm gonna be a contestant on television.
他们还没有告诉我什么时后上
They haven't told me when yet,
不过一定会很骄傲的,
but you'll be proud
当你看到妈妈穿上红礼服 金鞋子上电视时
when you see your mother in her red dress on TV.
上电视有什么大不了?
What is the big deal?
那些药在你上电视前会要你的命
Those pills will kill you before you get on.
“没什么大不了?. ”
"Big deal? "
坐计程车的时后
You drove up in a cab.
你知道谁坐最好的位子吗?
Did you see who had the best seat?
我现在是有名的人了 哈瑞
I'm somebody now, Harry.
大家都喜欢我
Everybody likes me.
过不久…
Soon...
成千上万的人会看到我
millions of people will see me
而且会喜欢我
and they'll all like me.
我会跟他们谈到你…
I'll tell them about you...
还有你爸爸
and your father.
他对我们有多好
How good he was to us.
记得吗?
Remember?
它是早上起床的理由
It's a reason to get up in the morning.
也是减肥的理由
It's a reason to lose weight,
为了能穿上那件红礼服
to fit in the red dress.
它是微笑的理由
It's a reason to smile.
它让明天更美好
It makes tomorrow all right.
我得到了什么 哈瑞?
What have I got, Harry?
嗯?
Hmm?
为什么我还要整理床
Why should I even make the bed
洗碗盘?
or wash the dishes?
这些我都做 但我为何要做?
I do them, but why should I?
我很孤单
I'm alone.
你爸爸走了 你也离家了
Your father's gone, you're gone.
我没有人可以…
I got no one to...
照顾
care for.
我得到了什么 哈瑞?
What have I got, Harry?
我很寂寞
I'm lonely.
我老了
I'm old.
你有朋友呀 妈
You got friends, Ma.
那不一样的
It's not the same.
她们不需要我
They don't need me.
我喜欢这样的感觉
I like the way I feel.
我喜欢想着红礼服
I like thinking about the red dress...
想着电视 还有你跟你爸爸
and the television and you and your father.
现在我看到阳光 都带着笑容
Now when I get the sun, I smile.
我会回来看你的 妈
I'll come and visit, Ma.
我现在按步就班
Now that I'm straight,
我的生意也上轨道 我会回来的
m-my business is going good, I'll come.
我和玛丽会回来吃晚餐
Me and Marion, we'll come for dinner.
好呀 你带她来
Good. You bring her.
我会做蘑菇汤跟烧烤给你们吃
I'll make you mushroom soup and a roast.
这样不错 妈 很棒
That sounds great, Ma. That sounds great.
- 我会先打个电话回来 好吗? - 好
- I'll call ahead, all right? - OK.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
我很高兴你有个不错的女朋友
I'm glad you have a nice girl
还有自己的生意 我很高兴
and your own business. I'm glad.
我该走了 妈
I gotta go, Ma.
我待会儿在曼哈顿跟人有约
I got an appointment in Manhattan in a little bit
不过我会回来的
but I'll be back.
- 好 你…你还有家里钥匙吗?
- OK, y-you still got your key?
- 嗯 我有 妈
- Yeah, I got it, Ma.
再见 儿子
Bye, Son.
布迪说你反应快
Brody says you comin' up quick.
谢啦 老兄
oh. Thanks, man.
他说你很聪明
He says you're smart,
忠诚l 而且不是个毒鬼
you're loyal and you're not a junkie.
布迪想提拔你
Brody wants to promote you.
让你承担更多责任 有兴趣吗?
Give you more responsibility. Interested?
有 当然!
Yeah, yeah!
当然有 老兄
Shit, yeah, man.
布迪说你背判他的话 他会杀了你
Brody says, you fuck him, I kill you.
- 我知道 - 记住
- I got that. - Remember that.
靠! 你有个白人司机!
Shit! You got a white driver!
干!
Fuck!
搞什么呀?
What the fuck?
别动!
Don't move!
我爱你 哈瑞
I love you, Harry.
你让我觉得像个人
You make me feel like a person.
像我自己
Like I'm me...
让我觉得很美
and I'm beautiful.
你本来就很美
You are beautiful.
你是世上最美的女人
You're the most beautiful girl in the world.
我的梦人情人
You're my dream.
'不 哥德太太 我很确定 我已经查过了'
'No, I'm certain. I've checked again.'
可能你们上次给我的药效较弱
But maybe you gave me a weaker one last time.
'不可能的
'That isn't possible.
药效都是一样的.'
They're all the same potency.'
可是感觉不一样呀
But something isn't the same.
'你只是渐渐习惯了
'You're becoming adjusted to them.
没什么好担心的 好吗?'
It's nothing to worry about, OK?'
- '我们有了优胜者!' - '有了优胜者!'
- 'We got a winner!' - 'We got a winner!'
'她很漂亮, 极有幽默感
'She's beautiful, with a winning sense of humour
'和魔法般的笑容
'and magical smile.
'来自布鲁克林 布莱顿滩 让我们热烈欢迎
'From Brighton Beach, Brooklyn, let's welcome
'哥德莎拉女士!'
'Mrs Sara Goldfarb!'
'莎啦来劲! 莎啦来劲! 噢 莎拉!
'Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh, Sara!
'莎啦热情有劲! 莎啦热情有劲! 噢 莎拉!'
'Sara's got juice! Sara's got juice! Ohh, Sara!'
嗨 泰隆
Love, Tyrone C.
收拾一下你的东西 有人来保你了
Get your shit together. You made bail.
多少钱?
How much?
花了我们大部份的现金 你行情涨高了
Most of our cash. You're up for consortin'.
噢 靠 他妈的!
oh, shit, man!
安杰拉说
Angel says
意大利人跟黑人在争斗
there's a war between the Italians and Blacks.
货会留在佛罗里达
Sal the Geep is keeping the shit in Florida
除非布迪的势力消失
until Brody's gone.
靠
Shit.
- 没有人可以拿到货 - 除了提姆老大
- No one's got a thing. - Except Big Tim.
靠. 我们去找他
Shit. Let's go see him.
他不卖的 只给娘们
He only givin' up for pussy.
什么?
What?
娘们. 他喜欢这一套 老兄
Pussy. He's hooked on it, man.
我说我会满足他要的
I'd give him all he wants.
他嫌我不够漂亮
He said I ain't cute enough.
'来吧 第叁项!
'Come on, number three!
'这会让很多人发疯
'This drives most people crazy.
'他们不会喜欢的
'They're not gonna like it.
'到现在都还算容易!
'This is easy so far!
戒除30天 就会…'
Give it up for 30 days, it will...'
你还好吧?
You all right?
嗯. 只是个恶梦
Yeah. It was just a bad dream.
要喝点水吗?
Want some water?
也许我们现在该打一点
Maybe we should dip in now.
好了!玛丽 我跟你说过了 好吗?
Come on! I already told you, all right?
我们就剩这一点了
It's all we have.
泰隆早上会再带点来的 哈瑞
Tyrone is gonna score in the morning, Harry.
我不知道 只是…
I don't know, it's...
只是发点劳骚
it's a bitch out there.
没事的
It'll be OK.
会没事的 哈瑞
It'll be OK, Harry.
是呀…
Yeah...
我想是吧
I guess so.
我爱你 哈瑞
I love you, Harry.
有什么问题吗? 体重正常
What's the problem? The weight's fine.
体重正常 我可不
The weight's fine, I'm not.
电冰箱…
The refrigerator...
怎么了?
Something wrong?
每样东西都…
Everything's...
都混在一起了
all mixed up.
- 好杂乱… - 没什么好担心的
- Confused... - Nothing to worry about.
填好这张表 约下星期看诊时间
Get this filled. Make an appointment for a week.
怎么了?
Well?
泰还没有拿到东西
Ty ain't found nothin' yet.
那我们怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧 你要想点办法 哈瑞
Well, you have to do something, Harry.
都是你 我们早上才没有东西
It's your fault we don't have anything.
- 你在说什么? - 你昨晚激动得把剩的都用完了
- What? - You were all hot last night.
- 简直胡扯!
- That is such bullshit!
- 你大可不用那样 我们就有东西了…
- We could've had something...
我会想要看你受苦
Was I supposed to watch you push off
自己置身事外吗?
and not go myself?
别都往我身上推 好吗?
Don't put it all on me, OK?
别担心 老兄 我们会再装满它的
Don't worry, man. We'll fill it up again.
情况会好转的
Things'll get better,
到时我们就能再装满它的 懂吗?
then we'll be fillin' the box back up, you know?
想听听新的消息吗?
So, you wanna hear the news?
什么消息?
What news?
有好消息 也有坏消息
You got your good news, you got your bad news.
说吧!
Shoot.
好消息是
Good news is,
再过几天街上就会出现高档货
there's gonna be some prime on the street.
- 是吗? - 嗯
- Really? - Mm-hm.
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
- 安杰拉 - 是喔?
- Angel. - Yeah?
大盘放话
Sal the Geep sent word
在圣诞期间放点东西出来
to let a couple of keys go for Christmas,
他是个好的基督徒
him being a good Christian and all,
不想破坏过节的气氛
not wantin' bad feelin' during the season.
- 你信吗? - 嗯 相信…
- You believe it? - Well, I did...
直到我听到了坏消息
till I heard the bad news.
什么?
Yeah?
价格加倍 还得按重量买
Price is double. You have to cop for weight.
- 至少一半的基本量 - 多少?
- At least a half a piece. - How much?
- 2块 - 2块?
- Two. - Two?
- 神经病呀! - 不然又能怎样?
- That's fuckin' insane! - What you gonna do?
羊毛出在羊身上 这是一定的
Man ain't gonna lay no nickel bag on ya.
我们去哪拿到2块?
Where we gonna get two?
你是说阿诺?
You mean Arnold?
是呀 你父母又不回你电话
Well, your parents won't even return your call.
我几个月没见过他了
I haven't seen him in months.
- 又如何? 他还是有打电话给你 不是吗?
- So? He's still callin', ain't he?
- 我不知道
- I don't know.
听着 我不知道还有什么其它办法
Look, I don't know what else to do.
这是我们重回计划的最后机会了!
It's our last chance to get back on track!
我们不用再每天争吵
We won't have to squabble
然后彼此僵在那!
and make the freezing scene every day!
我们须要钱
We need the bread.
赚钱不是问题 哈瑞
Getting the money is not the problem, Harry.
那到底问题是什么?
What is the problem?
我不知道该怎么弄到钱
I don't know what I'll have to do to get it.
听着…
Look...
宝贝…
Baby...
我们会很快再展开生意
we'll be back in business in no time.
重新再动起来
We'll start movin' again,
还会开始累积财富
and we'll start savin'.
一且会很完美 像原本那样
It'll be perfect, just like it was.
我保证 玛丽
I promise, Marion.
你看着吧
You'll see.
不 我只是 嗯…
No, I've just, uh..
我好像 永远得染上感冒似的
. I've had this flu forever, it seems like.
- 你忧郁吗?
- Are you depressed?
- 不 不是那样的
- No, it's nothing like that.
我一直 嗯… 我一直都很忙
I've been, uh... I've been really busy.
事实上, 我一直在做设计…没停过
Actually, I've been designing... non-stop.
太好了 很高兴知道你有所斩获
Wonderful. Glad to hear you've been productive.
明白得说吧
To be perfectly frank,
接到你的电话我很惊讶
I was a little surprised to hear from you.
- 有什么问题吗? - 没有 为何这样问?
- Is there something wrong? - No. Why?
嗯 通常是这样子的...
Well, it's usually the case...
接到许久没消息的人电话
from someone you haven't heard from.
一切都很好
Everything's fine.
事实上
Actually,
我有点事相求
I have a favour to ask.
王八蛋!
You smug fuck!
什么呢?
What is it?
我需要点钱
I need some money.
我能知道你为何需要钱吗?
May I ask what for?
- 把灯关掉好吗?
- Could you turn the light off?
- 为什么想关灯呢?
- Why do you want the light off?
没有为什么
I just do.
- 你没做过吗? - 拜托 阿诺
- You never did before. - Please, Arnold.
- 人到哪去了? - 我不知道 老兄
- Where is everybody? - I don't know, man.
安杰拉只说在沃德邦超市碰面
All Angel said was meet at Waldbaum's.
- 确定是这一家吗?
- Is this the right Waldbaum's?
- 对 我确定
- Yeah, I'm positive.
你只要帮我留意 我也帮你留意
You just watch my back, and I'll watch yours.
- 我们现在该怎么办? - 嘿
- What are we supposed to do now? - Hey.
真是人山人海
Everyone and their mother.
车子要来了 后退
The truck's gonna be here. Back up.
往后退
Back up.
回来!
Come back!
去他妈的药头!
Stupid fuckin' junkie!
我们被耍了
We're fucked! We are fucked.
妈的 他们在佛洲坐热太阳
Sitting in that hot-ass sun
我们却要坐在这寒冷的冰雪中
while we sit here ass deep in motherfuckin' snow.
再回去看看不知道会怎样?
What if we went down there?
- 你是认真的吗? - 为什么不?
- Are you serious? - Why not?
你在鬼扯些什么?
What the fuck are you sayin'?
你想你可以攀得上关系吗?
We ask some room clerk at some hotel for a connection?
你不把握机会吗?
You saying you can't nose out some dope
当货来的时候
when it's around?
老兄 我们没什么好失去的了 现在是大好时机
Man, we got nothin' to lose. It's wide open.
如果我们马上回去的话
And if we get there right away
要卖多少价格就由我们来订
we can name our own price,
还可让那群白痴为我们上街头
and have those fools cover the street for us.
是呀 老兄
Yeah, man.
去年夏天真他妈的开心 不是吗?
Last summer was a motherfuckin' ball, huh, Jim?
就好像有千年那么久
Just seems like a thousand years ago
了至去年夏天
since last summer, man.
我们会再像那时一样的 老兄
It'll be like that again, man.
我可以叫安杰拉给我们简短的
I could get Angel to get us a short...
如果我们能保证给他高档海洛因
if we promise him some dynamite scag.
感谢老天. 你去哪了?
Thank God. Where have you been?
你以为我们去哪了?
Where the hell you think I've been?
- 东西呢? - 我们碰到了一点麻烦
- Where's the score? - We had a bit of a problem.
我是说 每样事情都还好,只是
I mean, everything was goin' good, and then...
- 有些人渣药头… - 怎么了?
- some dumb-ass junkie... - Did what?
有些人渣药头怎么了?! 你搞砸了是吗?!
Some dumb-ass junkie did what?! You fucked up?!
- 你在发什么神经?
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- 你保证过不会有问题的! 记得吗?
- You promised it was gonna be OK.
我为了你跟那个混球搞
I fucked that sleaze-bag.
为了你我什么都做了!
I put myself through hell for you!
- 就是没有货嘛!
- There's nothing out there!
- 我才不管! 妈的死无赖!
- I don't give a shit! Fucking loser!
你就是以为我们还有就对了?
You wanna be sure we have some extra?
泰告诉我有个家伙有一些
Ty told me about a guy holding some weight.
不过他不卖的!
But he ain't sellin' it!
'喂?'
'Yeah?'
- 给我那家伙的电话 - '哪个?'
- Gimme that guy's number. - 'What guy?'
- 喜欢娘们那个! - '为什么?'
- The guy who likes broads! - 'Why?'
告诉我就对了!
Just gimme the number!
'好拉. 934-8777.'
'All right. 934-8777.'
你这么烦的话, 去跟他搞在一块吧!
You worried so much, go fix yourself up with him!
这样就不须要再等了
You won't have to fuckin' wait
我也不用在街头上受冻了
and I won't freeze my ass off the fucking street!
妈的
Fuck you.
'好的 优胜者出现了'
'All right, we got a winner.'
- '优胜者' - '优胜者出现了'
- 'We got a winner.' - 'We got a winner.'
'她不但美丽
'She's beautiful,
还有过人的幽默和神奇的笑容
with a winning sense of humour and smile.
'她将赢得你们的心!
'She'll win your heart!
'来自布鲁克林 布莱顿滩
'From Brighton Beach, Brooklyn,
'让我们热烈欢迎
'please give a juicy welcome to
哥德莎拉太太!'
our own Mrs Sara Goldfarb!'
'莎拉热情有劲! 莎拉热情有劲! 噢 莎拉!'
'Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh, Sara!'
'噢 莎拉!'
'Ohh, Sara!'
'真高兴到来这来'
'It's a pleasure to be here.'
'很高兴你来参加节
'It's a pleasure to have you.
目 你的服装真是出色
And that is one smashing dress.'
'谢谢你. 泰皮
'Thank you. Tappy.
如果你不介意 我想跟我先生
I would like to say hello
西蒙打声招呼
to my husband, Seymour,
'还有我那英俊有为的儿子…'
'and my beautiful, successful son Harold...'
'我希望你活在爱中
'I hope you're in love.
'请来看我,
'Please come and see me,
顺便把玛丽带来 好吗?'
and bring Marion, won't you?'
'我想他很快会来的
'I'm sure he'll be here soon.
'差不多是时候了 你准备好了吗?'
'It's almost that time. Are you ready?'
'我好了 泰皮'
'I'm ready, Tappy.'
'别担心 别担心'
'Not to worry. Not to worry.'
你在那做什么?
What are you doing here?
你怎么会在这?
Why are you here?
- 你想干嘛? - 噢 泰皮!
- What do you want? - Oh, Tappy!
'加入我们一起创造卓越
'Join us in creating excellence.
'噢 我以为你不会叫我'
'Oh, I thought you'd never ask.'
你看这个
Look at this.
- 真呕心 - 你想怎样呢?
- It's disgusting. - What do you expect?
你能做得更好吗?
Could you do any better?
看这个
Look at this.
这是栋老建
It's an old building.
有几年没粉刷过了
It hasn't been painted in years.
我老了! 孤独一人!
I'm old! Alone!
你不了解的
You don't understand.
拜托 我会解释的
Please. I'll explain.
那是什么? 不 我不要!
What is that? No, I don't want that!
你在干什么? 离我远一点!
What are you doing? Get away from me!
- 开始罗 哥德太太 - 什么开始了?
- Ready, Mrs Goldfarb. - Ready for What?
叁 二…
Three, two...
我要做什么?
What am I supposed to do?
我!
Feed me!
我
Feed him yourself.
-   我 莎拉 -   我 莎拉
Feed me, Sara.
我 莎拉!
Feed me, Sara!
我 莎拉!   我 莎拉!
Feed me, Sara! Feed me, Sara!
我只是想上电视! 拜托!
I just wanna be on television! Please!
谢拉 安杰拉
Thank you, Angel.
噢-噢!
Whoo-hoo!
希望这样行得通
Sure hope this motherfucker works.
我的屁股可以好好热一下
My ass could use some heat.
- 要多久才会到?
- How long this trip's gonna take?
- 我会在一天内到达
- We'll make it in a day.
一天? 靠!
A day? Shit!
加州 我们来了
California, here we come.
是佛罗里达 泰 佛州
It's Florida, Ty. Florida.
加州 佛州…
California, Florida...
两个都可让白屁股晒黑是吧
Either way, your pale ass getting a tan.
啊!
Ah!
这辆列车有到麦迪逊大道吗?!
Does this train go to Madison Avenue?!
你认识默林跟布洛克吗?
Do you know Maylin and Block?
我有他们的地址. 在麦迪逊大道上
I have their address. It's on Madison Avenue.
- 我就要上电视了 - 你累坏了!
- I'm gonna be on television. - You're whacked!
嘿! 嘿! 哈罗?
Hey! Hey! Hello?
你知道这辆列车有到麦迪逊大道?
Do you know if this train goes to Madison Avenue?
我要上电视了!
I'm gonna be on television!
我只想知道什么时候
I just have to find out when.
佛罗里达?
Florida?
他什么时候回来?
When is he gonna be back?
几天后? 安杰拉 我该怎么办?
A few days? Angel, what am I supposed to do?
你一定要帮我
Please, you gotta help me.
噢 好啦 我可以给你钱
Oh, come on, I can get you money.
安杰拉 无论如何一定要
Angel, there's gotta be something. Anything.
帮我
Help me.
你怎么不打电话给我呢?
Why aren't you calling me?
我要知道我什么时候上电视
I have to know when I'm gonna be on television.
我是莎拉哥德
I'm Sara Goldfarb.
你应该告诉我
And you should tell me
什么时候要上电视
when I'm gonna be on television.
请稍坐一会 我会通知他们
Just sit for a moment. I'll ring them.
我只是想知道什么时候
I just wanna know when.
也许你弄丢了我的资料!
Maybe you lost my card!
拜托, 请看一下 然后就可以告诉我了
Please, have a look, and you'll tell me.
不是为了得奖 我会把奖给别人的
It's not the prizes. I'll give them away.
我只想上节目
I just wanna be on the show.
我等了好久
I've waited so long...
跟我的儿子哈瑞还有我的小孙子
to be on with my Harry and my grandson.
来 哥德太太 慢慢喝
Here, Mrs Goldfarb, sip this.
有时要一阵子
Sometimes it takes a while
才能通知你上电视
to get called for a show,
哥德太太
Mrs Goldfarb.
噢
Oh. Oooh.
- 是她吗? - 是的
- Is this her? - Yes.
- 你能走吗? - 我可以走台步!
- Can you walk? - I'm walkin' across the stage!
你一定要看看我家哈瑞上电视
And you should see my Harry on television.
我们会把奖给别人
We're giving the prizes away.
我只是想上节目!
I just wanted to be on the show!
- 她叫什么名字? - 应该是莎拉哥德吧
- What's her name? - We think it's Sara Goldfarb.
跟西蒙说在美容院跟我碰面
Tell Seymour to meet me at the beauty parlour.
我穿了
I've got the red dress that
参加哈瑞毕业典礼的那件红礼服
I wore to Harry's graduation and gold shoes.
好了 哥德太太. 我们走吧
oK, Mrs Goldfarb. Here we go.
一 二 叁…
- One, two, three...
放轻松慢慢来
Let's take it nice and easy.
'喂?'
'Yeah?'
嗨…
Hi...
告诉罗丝说我要上电视了
Tell Rose I'm going to be on television.
噢
Whoo.
噢 靠!
oh, shit!
天呀! 你有那玩意多久了?
God damn! How long you had that?
- 只有几天
- Just a few days.
- 那东西看起来不太好
- That shit don't look too good.
我也觉得不是很舒服 老兄
It don't feel too good either, man.
不过来点海洛因就会没事了
But a little stuff will take care of that.
嘿! 不要打在那里!
Hey! Don't shoot in there!
不这样的话 血管会爆开
I'll blow it if I don't.
妈的
Fuck it.
噢…
oh...
靠
Shit.
- 嗨 还好吗? 听得到吗?
- Hi, how are you? Can you hear me?
- 嗯 西蒙
- Yes, Seymour.
- 有吃了什么吗?
- Take anything?
- 我穿了红礼服还有…
- I took my red dress and...
- 非紧急状况. 带她到精神科
- No emergency. Take her to psych.
- 电视
- Television.
进来吧
Come on in.
谢谢
Thanks.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
玛丽
Marion.
嗯 你知道吗?
Well, what do you know?
罗宾汉里的少女玛丽
Maid Marion.
我是小约翰
I'm little John.
你这里景色不错
Beautiful view.
你知道我喜欢小女生什么吗?
You know what I like about paddy chicks?
她们口技都不错
They give good head.
黑妞们就是不会口交
Black broads know nothin' about head.
不知道为什么
I don't know why.
可能是按部落传统来做的吧
Maybe it's to do with some ancient tribal custom.
来吧
Come here.
嗯. 最好留点体力
Mmm. Better save some of that energy.
噢 我知道它很漂亮 宝贝
oh, I know it's pretty, baby,
但我不放它出来亮相
but I didn't take it out for air.
好呀
Yeah.
我跟你说过离那只手臂远一点. 知道吗?
I told your ass, stay away from that arm. See?
我得打电话给玛丽 老兄
I gotta call Marion, man.
现在来说那可是长途电话罗
That's about to be a long-distance call now.
600哩了!
That's 600 miles!
我们接近了迈阿密600哩了
We are 600 miles closer to Miami.
是呀 也远离纽约600哩了 泰
It's also 600 miles further away from New York.
你知道吗 我还有真正好口味的货
I know where to get a real nice taste,
虽然有点竞赛的味道 星期天晚上t?
though it's more like play. Sunday night?
我们发起了一个聚会
We're throwing a little gathering.
大家人都很好
All good people.
不行 我没空
I can't, I'm busy.
反正我的瘾不是很重
Anyway, I'm not really hooked.
噢 我知道 但是口味真的不错
Oh, I know, but it's a real nice taste.
星期天见了 少女玛丽
I'll see you Sunday, Maid Marion.
好了 哥德太太 试着回答我的问题
OK, just try and answer my questions.
- 你什么时候开始服用药片?
- When did you start taking pills?
- 噢 夏天时
- Oh, the summer.
- 你从去年夏天开始服用?
- You started last summer?
- 我得到做日光浴最棒的位子
- I got the best place in the sun.
- 艾达帮我整理头发
- Ada fixed my hair.
- 一切都会很好的
- Everything is gonna be all right.
我们很快就会帮你整修
We'll get you fixed up in no time.
- 撑着点 老兄 - 我真的撑不下去了
- Hold tight, man. - I can't fucking cut it.
我得为我的手臂想点办法
I gotta do something about my arm.
让我看看怎么了
Let me see what it looks like.
噢 天呀 靠!
oh, damn, Jim!
噢
oh, man.
我没看过这么呕心的东西
That's one ugly motherfucker.
- 我要打给玛丽 - 真他妈的
- I gotta call Marion. - Fuck that.
你非上医院不可了 老兄
We gotta get you to a hospital, man.
那是什么?
What is that?
我不要 我不要!
I don't want that. I don't want that!
啊! 呃…
Ah! Oh...
什么问题?
What's the problem?
- 我的手臂 我的手臂痛得要命
- It's my arm. My arm is killin' me.
- 我来看一下
- let's have a look at it.
好吧
All right.
我等一下就回来
I'll be back in a minute.
我想通宵玩二十一点
I wanna play blackjack all night long.
所以我就来排班.
So I make up this routine.
我说 “尽管去吧. 我不是很舒服”
I say, "you go ahead. I don't feel good."
很显然的 他们离开了…
Sure enough, they leave...
好了吗? 一 二 叁
Ready? One, two and three.
他们一离开
As soon as they leave,
我马上跑回赌场
I go running back to the casino,
坐在二十一点台桌上
sit at my blackjack table.
我整晚都泡在那里
I am there for the whole night.
最后 我赢了不少
Finally, I get up so big,
我口袋里有五个一百的黑色筹码
I got five $100 black chips in my pocket.
我发誓 时间过得真快
I swear to God. The hours are going by.
我回来时 跟一个十七岁辣妹搭讪
I'm laying back, hittin' on hard 17 s.
真是漂亮
It was beautiful.
接着我所知道的
Next thing I know,
那是一位安全人员
this security guard
坐在一旁 叫我非离开不可
is sitting there telling me I have to leave.
我说 “你为什么说我要离开?”
I'm like, "Why you telling me I have to leave?"
他说, “你要离开是因为…”
He says, "You have to leave because..."
吞下
Swallow.
吞下去
哥德太太 你非吃点东西不可
You have to eat.
你要吃东西才能维持健康
If we're gonna get you healthy you have to eat.
跟护理人员配合一下 好吗?
Work with the attendants.
我会试一些新的药看看
I'm gonna try some new medications.
- 哈罗 - '玛丽'
- Hello. - 'Marion.'
哈瑞?
Harry?
'玛丽 我一直都好想你
'Marion, I've been thinking about you so much.
'你好吗?'
'Are you OK?'
- 你什么时候回家? - 快了
- When you comin' home? - Soon.
什么时候?
When?
就快了
Soon.
- '你坚持一下好吗?' - 哈瑞?
- 'You holdin' out all right?' - Harry?
你今天能回来吗?
Can you come today?
嗯
Yeah.
我会回去
I'll come.
'我今天会回去'
'I'll come today.'
只管等着我 好吗?
You just wait for me, all right?
- 好 哈瑞 - '我就回去了 玛丽'
- OK, Harry. - 'I'm coming back, Marion.'
- 嗯 - '玛丽?'
- Yeah. - 'Marion?'
怎了?
Yeah?
我真的很抱歉 玛丽
I'm really sorry, Marion.
我了解
I know.
哥德太太?
Mrs Goldfarb?
你还好吗?
You all right?
嗯 是这样的 哥德太太
Um, so, Mrs Goldfarb,
我们已经试过多种药物治疗
we've tried several medications,
不过好像都没什么效果
and you don't seem to be responding.
我想我们会
I believe we might want to
试着采用非常态性治疗
try some alternative methods.
我们的脑电汤治疗在过去有不错的结果
We've had excellent results with ECT in the past.
嗯… 只要你可以…
Um... So if I can just...
填好保险的表单…
get your John Hancock...
我们就可以进行了
we'll get underway.
太好了. 谢谢
Great. Thanks.
噢 天呀!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
我需要医生 老兄
I need a doctor, man.
我的朋友病了 帮他一下 拜托
My friend is sick. Give him some help, please.
我受不了了 老兄! 我的手臂! 我他妈的手臂!
I can't take it, man! My arm! My fuckin' arm!
救我!
Help me!
帮帮我们! 来个人帮帮忙吧 拜托!
Help us! Somebody fuckin' help us, please!
少女玛丽. 欢迎
Maid Marion. Welcome.
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
听得到? 看得到吗?
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
伙伴们 认识一下玛丽吧
Fellas, meet Marion.
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
好戏上场了
Show time.
好的 可以工作 听得到? 看得到吗?
OK for work. Can you hear me? Can you see me?
是 呃!
Yes. Oof!
说 “长官”. 妈的纽约毒瘾黑鬼
Say, "sir". Goddam New York dope fiend niggers.
学点礼貌
Learn some manners.
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.
- 戴上护齿套
- Got a mouthpiece.
- 听得到? 看得到吗?
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
听说他的手臂有点问题
Says something's wrong with his arm.
我想他没有办法再打药在那里了
He won't be puttin' any more dope in that.
- 闻起来比他还糟 - 试机
- Smells worse than he do. - Test.
先把他带到医院去
Get him over to hospital.
好了吗? 来…一
Ready? And... one.
那是你们这些毒虫的通病
That's the trouble with you dope fiends.
你们态度很差. 知道吗?
You got a rotten attitude. You know that man?
- 现在我们要做什么? - 屁眼对屁眼
- So what are we gonna do now? - Ass to ass.
屁眼对屁眼!
Ass to ass!
把你那玩意放进自己的屁眼吧! 来吧!
Put your spineless back into it! Come on!
好了吗? 来…二!
Ready? And... two!
屁眼对屁眼!
Ass to ass!
- 放进去! - 就是这样
- Put it in there! - That's it.
放轻松慢慢来
Nice and easy.
马玲薯泥!
Mashed potatoes!
接近了 给我一斤吧. 对了
Here's the close. I need one gram. Bingo.
别放弃 别放弃
Don't give up. Don't give up.
加油 加油 加油!
Move it, move it, move it!
好了
OK.
好了吗? 来…叁!
Ready? And... three!
射吧! 射吧! 射吧! 射吧!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
我们得从肩膀以下切除才行
We're gonna take it off at the shoulder.
射吧! 射吧! 射吧! 射吧!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
锯子
Saw.
玛丽!
Marion!
没事了
It's all right.
别担心. 你在医院里
Don't worry. You're in a hospital.
- 玛丽? - 谁?
- Marion? - Who's that?
我们会通知她 她会来的
She'll be sent for. She'll come.
- 不. - 不要?
- No. - No?
不 她不会来
No, she won't.
她会来的
She'll come.
优胜者出来了 优胜者出来了
- We got a winner. - We got a winner.
优胜者来了! 优胜者出来了
- Got a winner! - We got a winner.
我们的新优胜者 就是有着人见人爱的性格
Our next winner is that delightful personality,
来自布鲁克林 布莱顿滩
from Brighton Beach, Brooklyn.
请热烈欢迎
Please, give a juicy welcome
哥德莎拉太太!
to Mrs Sara Goldfarb!
很高兴告诉你
I'm delighted to tell you
你赢得了首奖!
that you have won the grand prize!
- 噢 不会吧! - 让我告诉你赢得了些什么
- Oh, no! - let me tell you what you've won.
他有迷人的笑容 跟自己的事业
He has a sweet smile and his own business.
他刚订完婚
He just got engaged,
而且将在今年夏天完成终身大事
and is about to get married this summer.
让我们热情地欢迎
Please give a warm and juicy welcome.
哥德哈瑞先生!
Harry Goldfarb!
哈瑞热情有劲! 哈瑞热情有劲!
Juice by Harry! Juice by Harry!
噢 哈瑞真来劲! 哈瑞真来劲!
ohh, Harry's got juice! Harry's got juice!
噢 哈瑞!
ohh, Harry!
- 我爱你 哈瑞 - 我也爱你 妈
- I love you, Harry. - I love you too, Ma.